hunkdujour.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy : Hunk du Jour

**Your Privacy**

The Hunk du Jour web site and HDJ Media, LLC (hereafter identified as "Hunk du Jour") is committed to protecting your privacy. We use personal information to verify commenter identity, track site usage, and provide content delivery.

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

When you visit our website, our server records standard log information. This includes your IP address, as well as the full URL of the page that you are visiting. We also implement the services of external tracking providers. Please see information about these external providers below.

When you leave a comment on our website, we store all information that you type into the comment form. This includes your e-mail address and name. We do not publish information left in the "e-mail address" comment field, but may use this address to contact you about your comment.

When you send us a message via our "Contact Us" form, we receive all of the information you type into the form via an e-mail message. We do not publish information sent via e-mail without permission, but may contact you via the address provided in the form.

When you sign up to receive our content via e-mail, we receive e-mail notification of your sign-up. Please see the FeedBurner and FeedBlitz privacy policies in the list of external providers below.

When you subscribe to our RSS feed, your reading and clicking information is included in aggregate data provided to us by FeedBurner. Please see our external providers below.

**How does Hunk du Jour protect customer information?**

The databases and applications which store personal information on Hunk du Jour are protected by strong password. Our server is housed in a secure datacenter.

**What about "cookies"?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use temporary "session" cookies to maintain information about you current visit. This includes whether you have cast a "Hunk of the Day" vote, or proven that you are human by passing our "Please type this number" test.

**Will Hunk du Jour disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

Hunk du Jour does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Hunk du Jour may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

Hunk du Jour may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Hunk du Jour, our users, or others.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Hunk du Jour. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Hunk du Jour also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsiblity of the linked site and Hunk du Jour has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. Hunk du Jour cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.

**External Partnerships**

We have implemented code from the following trusted service providers on Hunk du Jour. These companies all maintain their own privacy policies.

Modurban Media  

**Questions and Feedback**

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://contact.asp/ "contact us").
